Anna Aghajanyan

818.747.8865• Los Angeles, CA • anna.aghajanyan987@gmail.com • <u>www.linkedin.com/in/aghajanyan-anna/</u> • <u>www.github.com/Anna02F</u> • <u>https://anna02f.github.io/My-portfolio-website/</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative, motivated, and passionate Frontend Developer with extensive experience in the banking industry. Highly effective at working and collaborating with team members to accomplish projects on time. Expertise in developing user interfaces for web applications and a responsive design using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, and other UI technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer, Kaput.am. Game startup, remote

01.2021 to 02.2022

Kaput.am is a fast-growing game startup that delivers online gaming experiences. Working as a side project.

- Increased user interaction by avg. 30% using competitive analysis and research.
- Gathered user requirements, designed new UI elements, and got positive feedback from users.
- Improved website performance by avg. 20% using optimization techniques.
- Collaborated with other developers to brainstorm project lunch ideas.
- Involved in using GIT for project management and version control.

Frontend Developer Intern, TCO LLC, remote

06.2019 to 06.2019

TCO LLC is an Armenian-based IT Startup, where I started my training and career as a UI Engineer intern.

- Converted design mockups into functional web applications using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Performed "Pixel-Perfect" implementation of the approved user interface app.
- Designed web pages and user applications that meet business and user goals through a positive user experience.

Accountant-Cashier, ARMECONOMBANK OISC, Yerevan, Armenia

12.2016 to 10.2018

ARMECONOMBANK is one of the largest banks in Armenia. Worked in a customer-centered environment.

- Performed all duties with high responsibility to ensure all deadlines were met on time.
- Ensured customer satisfaction with patience, open-mindedness, and a positive attitude.
- Processed 30+ customer transactions per hour with extreme attention to detail.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, React, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Responsive design, Browser Compatibility
- SEO best practices, Usability, Accessibility
- Basic Back-End: Node.js
- Version Control: Git

EDUCATION

Armenian State University of Economics, Master of Finance, Major in Securities Markets, *2014 to 2016* **Armenian State University of Economics**, Bachelor of Finance, Major in Securities Markets, *2010 to 2014*